https://www.healthstream.com/privacy-statement

NRP Help
Login Help
Contact
Looking to Buy?
Need Support?
THE WORLD’S FIRST DIGITAL MENTOR FOR NURSES
See how HealthStream uses artificial intelligence (AI) to personalize competency development and improve quality outcomes.
Learning
ARE LEADERS BORN... OR MADE?
Learn how HealthStream’s leadership development solution allows you to cultivate a culture of future leaders.
A New Approach to Mandatory Training
One solution to deliver, test, and measure your organization’s knowledge.
BLS, ALS, & PALS
Neonatal Resuscitation Program® (NRP®)
Browse All Courses
Learning
International Liaison Committee on Resuscitation (ILCOR)
Learn about the process ILCOR uses to create the treatment recommendations that influence resuscitation guidelines published throughout the world.
Optimize Reimbursement Through Engaging Education
We partner with the best in the industry to offer innovative ways to improve your revenue cycle education and workforce development.
Learning
The Industry Leader in Credentialing, Provider Enrollment, Privileging, and Evaluation
More than 2,500 hospitals and 1,300 medical groups rely on our powerful suite of products.
Privacy Statement
Last updated and effective as of August 20, 2019
Welcome to the HealthStream, Inc. website, available at www.healthstream.com (this “Site”). This Privacy Statement discloses the privacy policy (this “Policy”) for this Site and describes how HealthStream, Inc. (“HealthStream”, “we”, or “us”), the operator of this Site, collects, protects, discloses and uses information that applies to your access to and use of this Site, including your access and use of any online HealthStream Services (the “Services”). This Policy applies only to information collected through this Site and not to information collected offline or through any other websites (even if affiliated with HealthStream or linked to by this Site). HealthStream may modify this Policy at any time, in its discretion, and modifications are effective upon being posted on this Site. The use of the Site is governed by the Terms of Use (“Terms”), which is incorporated by reference. Please review the Terms before you use this Site. If you are unwilling to accept the terms and conditions of the Terms, please do not use this Site. You are responsible for reviewing this Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it.
This Policy is intended solely and exclusively for residents of the United States. Accordingly, this Policy is directed only towards residents of the United States. By using this Site, you represent that you are not a resident of the European Economic Area, including the European Union or Switzerland. If you are located outside of the United States, including in the European Union, and you use this Site, you are doing so in violation of Terms.
1. The Information We Collect.
Whenever you create a username and password, comment in a forum, or otherwise interact with this Site, HealthStream may collect personal information from or about you. We collect the following categories of information from or about you:
Contact Information: when you contact us using the forms or links on this Site, email us, or set up a user account, you are voluntarily providing us with your contact information including your name, email address, and telephone number.
Internet or other electronic network activity information: when you access or use this Site, we may collect your internet or other electronic network activity information, including your IP address and your interaction with this Site. Additionally, we may use Google Analytics and cookies to track your usage of the Site, whether you are a new or returning visitor, the pages that you visited, and the time you spent on each page.
Professional Information: when you sign up for an account, make a purchase on this Site, or contact us using the forms provided on this Site, we may collect your professional information, including your name, email address, employer, organizational affiliation, and telephone number that you provide us.
2.
How We Use the Information We Collected.
HealthStream may use the personal information you share with us in the following ways:
Contact or Professional Information: we may communicate with you about products and services we offer. If you would like to opt out of receiving marketing communications, please see Section 5 below. Please note, however, you cannot opt out of service related emails, including relating to a transaction you initiated or relating to any changes to our Terms, this Policy, or other policies or notices that may affect your access to and use of the services.
Internet or other electronic network activity information: we may communicate with you about products and services relevant to your organization. If you would like to opt out of receiving marketing communications, please see Section 5 below. Please note, however, you cannot opt out of service related emails, including relating to a transaction you initiated or relating to any changes to our Terms, this Policy, or other policies or notices that may affect your access to and use of the services. To What Extent We Disclose Information to Third Parties
(a)
Information Disclosed for a Business Purpose: HealthStream may disclose the information you shared with us to third parties for a business purpose. HealthStream may have disclosed the following categories of personal information about you to third parties for a business purpose in the preceding 12 months.
(b)
Service Providers: We may disclose your personal information with service providers for the provision, operation, maintenance, administration, promotion, improvement and oversight of this Site and our Services, or to fulfill your requests or transactions you initiate.
(c) Legal Compliance: We may disclose your personal information when required to do so by law or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to: i) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or regulatory bodies; ii) enforce our Terms or Policy or to protect the security or integrity of this Site and/or our Services; iii) exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of HealthStream, our users, or others.
3.
Notice to California Residents – Your California Privacy Rights.
(a) California “Shine the Light” Disclosure: We do not disclose your personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.
(b) California “Do Not Track” Disclosure: We have disclosed our collection practices herein, but at this time, we do not honor do-not-track signals. Some of the third parties that we work with may honor such requests.
(c) Right to Access: You may request from us the categories of personal information we have collected about you; the categories of sources from which the personal information was collected; the categories of third parties with whom we share personal information; and the specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you. You may also request the business or commercial purpose for collecting or personal information and the categories of personal information that we disclosed about you for a business purpose.
You will be required to provide verification of your request before we will honor your request and disclose the requested information. We are required to provide you with this disclosure no more than twice in a 12-month period; however, we may, at our discretion, honor additional requests.
(d) Right to Data Portability: You may request from us the categories and specific pieces of personal information collected about you, from whom it was collected, the specific business purposes for which it was collected, and with whom it was shared.
You will be required to provide verification of your request before we will honor your request and disclose the requested information. We are required to provide you with this disclosure no more than twice in a 12-month period; however, we may, at our discretion, honor additional requests.
We will provide this information by mail or electronically. If provided electronically, the information will be provided in a portable, and to the extent technically feasible, in a readily useable format that allows you to transmit this information to another entity without hindrance.
(e) Right to Delete: You may request deletion of your Personal information that we have collected from you.
You will be required to provide verification of your request upon submission of your request. There are certain circumstances under which we are not required to comply with your request for deletion. In such a scenario, we will advise you as to why we cannot honor your request.
(f) How to Exercise Your Rights: You may submit a request for disclosure of your Personal information collected or disclosed or for deletion of your Personal information through this Site or by calling this toll-free number: 800.521.0574.
If you have exercised your right to request disclosure of your Personal information collected or disclosed or for deletion of your Personal information, we will not discriminate against you for exercising such rights, including by denying you goods or services, by charging different prices or rates for such goods or services, providing a different level or quality of goods or services, or suggesting that you will receive a different price or rate, or different level or quality, for goods or services. We may, however, offer financial incentives for the collection of your Personal information, for the sale your Personal information, or for the deletion of your Personal information.
4.
Opt-Out; Retention.
We support the right of visitors to choose. If you decide that you do not wish to receive communications from us you can contact us at privacy@healthstream.com or at the address provided below, indicating that you no longer want to receive information relating to this Site. HealthStream will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.
5.
How to Change Your Information.
If you have signed up for an account, you may view and correct your account information at any time by logging into your account or by contacting us at the address below.
6.
Children’s Privacy.
This Site is not designed to solicit individuals under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect or store any personal information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of 16. If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of 16 in violation of this Policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe that we have any information from or about anyone under the age of 16, please contact us at the contact information specified below.
7.
Linking to Other Sites & Other Privacy Policies.
This Site may include links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from ours. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, your information is governed by the privacy policies of those other websites. You should carefully review the privacy policy of any website you visit.
8.
Protecting Your Personal Information.
Protecting your information is a shared responsibility. We use industry-standard technologies to protect your personal information. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your username and password. You can protect your information by monitoring your account and notifying us immediately of any changes or suspicious activity.
9.
Consent and Modifications to Policy.
This Site is controlled, operated, and administered entirely within the United States. By using this Site, you signify your agreement to the terms of this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not disclose any Personal information through this Site. This Policy and the use of this Site are governed by Tennessee law. Certain portions of this Site are restricted to users which have a separate agreement with HealthStream and other terms and conditions may apply to those services or products. All obligations with regard to HealthStream’s services or products governed by a separate agreement and this Policy shall not be construed to modify or alter any agreements relative to those products or services.
Users of the Site consent to the sole and exclusive jurisdiction and venue of such courts as the most convenient and appropriate for the resolution of disputes concerning this Policy. This Policy and the notices outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any third party.
10.
Questions, Comments and Feedback.
We welcome your questions, comments and all feedback pertaining to your privacy or any other issue with regard to this Site. You may contact us at:
Address:
HealthStream, Inc.
500 11th Avenue North
Suite 1000
Nashville, TN 37203
800.521.0574
Privacy Statement
Quick Links
About
Blog
HealthStream Acquires myClinicalExchange
HealthStream to Acquire ANSOS™ Staff Scheduling from Change Healthcare
Nexion Health to Improve Competency and Care with HealthStream New Online Training Tool
HealthStream, in Partnership with Association of periOperative Registered Nurses, Advances Resuscitation Education with First-in-the-Industry, Role-Based Simulation Program
HealthStream Acquires ShiftWizard
HealthStream Brands
HealthStream
VerityStream
Speak to a Solutions Expert
Clinical Development
Jane™
Onboard & Retain Nurses
Neonatal Resuscitation (NRP)
Looking to Buy?
Need Support?
